freshersvacancy.com 2010-07-20

# FreshersVacancy

## Privacy Policy

FreshersVacancy.com Privacy Statement has been developed with best endeavors to comply with best Privacy to the users of this website. Registrants must agree to their personal information being used by this website  in accordance with this Privacy Policy before they may register.

In order to register for this website , seekers registering individually must provide us with their name, mobile, and their email address.

The information collected from Registrants is used for the following purposes:

  * to send a confirmation notice to the Registrant of the registration;
  * to respond to any questions, concerns or problems raised by the Registrant;
  * to send out a newsletter or emails about the resources and services;

In all communications, Registrants may opt out at any time by following the specific opt out instructions within the communications we send.

A cookie is a little piece of information handed to a web browser from a web server that contains information that can be retrieved from the server later. When you visit the Site the server may attach a cookie to your computer’s memory. We  uses cookies only to the limited extent of recognizing the Registrant when they visit the Site and pairing that Registrant with the account (and account preferences) that the Registrant created. However, this information is not linked to any personal information that Registrant may provide and cannot be used to identify Registrants. You should be able to configure your computer so that it disables cookies or does not accept them.

**What is the DoubleClick DART cookie?**   
The [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) is used by Google in the ads served on the websites of its partners, such as websites displaying AdSense ads or participating in Google certified ad networks. When users visit a partner's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help better serve and manage ads on the publisher's site(s) and across the web.

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative [opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).) 

Please address all requests and questions about this privacy policy to the **Privacy and Data Protection Officer** and use the email address in the Contact section of the Site . ****
